这是一个空余的房间 不需要做太多的清洁
This is a spare room not much to clean in here.
这是女儿的房间
This is my daughter's.
- 顺便说一句 我很喜欢你的海报   - 谢谢
- I really like your poster by the way.   - Thanks.
我的天 你能想象在现场看他们的样子吗
God,can you imagine seeing them live.
我光是想想就已经起鸡皮疙瘩了
I think those bumps just thinking about it.
- 很高兴见到你   - 我也是
- Happy to see you.   - Me too.
我们都知道你能弹的更好
We both know you've played better.
- 我他妈的有权力过上幸福的生活  - 我也是
- I have right to be happy,goddamn it.   - So do I!
- 你和你妈吵架了吗   - 我恨她
- You and your mom gonna fight? - I hate her.
你不必做那些你不情愿做的事
You don't have to do anything you don't want to do.
- 我很高兴你在我身边   - 我也是
- I'm really glad you're here.   - Me too.
作为你的父亲 我自然很好奇你在做些什么
As your father I'm naturally curious about what you're doing.
担心是我的本能
I'm worried is what I am
- 我是警探齐尔 很高兴认识你 - 幸会
Detective Dozier,pleased to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
我对警察说我对你一无所知
I'm on record saying that I know anything about you
我也不知道你在哪里
and I have no idea where you are.
我只是不会告诉他们全部的真相
I just won't tell them all make something up.
- 他们不会相信你的 - 你又怎么知道呢
- They will never believe you.   - How do you know?
我想着我可以给你一点关于你妈的东西
I was wondering if I could give you some mom.
寻找我失踪女儿的海报
Missing posters of my daughter.
你又给自己招惹了什么麻烦
What kind of trouble have you got yourself in?
什么麻烦都没有
I've got myself anything.
我为了保护你而撒谎
I lied for you to protect you.
放我出去 劳拉 劳拉
I want to get out, Laura. Laura!